<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Doge Money</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="adnob_appid1">ca-app-pub-9062980565707854~1156398682</string>
    <string name="ads1">ca-app-pub-9062980565707854/7338663652</string>
    <string name="sample">ca-app-pub-7300440519666493~2860439544</string>
    <string name="dontchange">ca-app-pub-7300440519666493/9754025691</string>
    <string name="bandarbantxt">Bandarban is in chittagong division and situated in southeastern Bangladesh. it’s one the foremost engaging travel destination in Bangladesh for its adventurous characteristics and heavenly scenic beauty. This eventually gets extremely laborious to go away if anyone visits Bandarban. The scenic beauty can beyond any doubt attract your soul.</string>
    <string name="textone">ABOUT DOGEARN
DOGEARN is a future investing platform that consists all earning ways in one place.</string>
    <string name="texttwo">Making investment markets accessible and understandable to everyone – this the main idea of DOGEARN. In order to invest, earn and profit from Blockchain you need to be well prepared. In today’s fast-changing world, majority of people do not have time to learn. Even those who try often fail due to the complexity of these new technologies.</string>
    <string name="textthree">Get Affiliates  Earn up to 15 %
DOGEARN is a future investing platform that consists all earning ways in one place.</string>
    <string name="textfour">If you only join someone with your referral link, you get 30 coins and your referrals link will be opened to the account that will get 5 coins more liformation</string>
    <string name="textfive">Referral Program
If you only join someone with your referral link, you get 30 coins and your referrals link will be opened to the account that will get 5 coins.</string>
    <string name="textsix">join our telegram channel.Then submit your telegram username and telegram channel Screenshots then you free 50 dogecoin.</string>
    <string name="textseven">You will first download the application and then send us screenshot. Watch the video to learn how to do this. You will be given dogecoin to see your writing Minimum 100 maximum 5000 coin.</string>
    <string name="texteight">If you share it with your Facebook account then you will be given the link and picture.You will be given dogecoin to see your writing, like and comment minimum is 50 maximum 20000 coin.
Free 50-20000 Dogecoin</string>
    <string name="textnine">Here you will see how to make an account. Then how to give telegram usermane, how to download android apps, how to share apps link and website link is facebook. Then you upload youtube and give us its video link.</string>
    <string name="textten">Here you will see how to make an account,How to activate the account,Then how to give telegram usermane, how to download android apps, how to share apps link and website link is facebook.</string>

</resources>
